❤️ උපසිරැසි ගැන්වුම Mflix විසින් ❤️
🔥 අලුත්ම Tv Series,Movies බලන්න Mflix එක්ක එකතු වෙන්න 🔥
[Road to Success]
[Episode 11]
Where is he?
It's him.
He was following me.
I wasn't following her.
I was trying to find you.
He's my manager.
You have a manager?
There's nothing weird about
Nanton's coach having a manager, right?
What's wrong?
What's with your outfit?
Can't afford to buy a pair of pants?
You know nothing about fashion.
See this?
This is the "missing lower body" look.
It's really in style right now.
If you don't button up your coat now,
I'm seriously going to make
your lower half disappear.
So out of touch.
Ms. Lin.
I've heard so much about you.
Let me formally introduce myself.
I am Felix Yu,
Winfred's manager.
[Felix Yu, Manager of Yongchuan Hengjiu
Youth Football Club]
Too bad.
I honestly thought
you were an exhibitionist,
and I wanted to test
how strong your mentality was.
You guys carry on.
I'll leave you alone.
I get your fashion.
Seeing is believing.
She really is an interesting girl.
Did you come here just to mooch off mine?
Let me tell you, they wouldn't fit.
They're too long for you.
This is called fashion taste.
Fashion taste.
What do you know?
Seriously.
"Fashion."
So, still two teaspoons of sugar?
Giving me coffee at this hour?
Are you trying to keep me up
and torture me all night?
I'll have water.
Alright then.
Water, water, water. Okay.
Here's your water.
So,
you're certain
that she's not Spade Q?
She's not.
Bro, I remember you were a materialist.
When did you become an idealist?
Do you really think someone
who's cute, a bit scatterbrained,
emotional,
and considerate of others
could be the kind of ruthless person
who sets up traps to lead people
to their deaths?
Would you put training wheels on a bike
and force yourself to ride it
just to win a bet?
♪ Two souls aligned ♪
♪ In silent gravity ♪
Would you cheat on a bet
by having your students help you
meet your exercise targets?
♪ Heal my heart ♪
Would you plot against your neighbor,
♪ With every part of you ♪
only to end up scaring yourself?
Would you do something just for laughs,
♪ Our words flow ♪
then end up using your neighbor's
washing machine?
♪ A gentle stream ♪
Besides,
she was willing to put her own life
on the line
to save a student.
♪ They glow like fireflies ♪
Do you think Spade Q would ever do that?
♪ Inside a silken dream ♪
The last time you talked this much
was when you were making a case for Jason.
♪ We talk the cool night, breeze away ♪
Anyway, when it comes to these details,
I think they're more convincing
than any data could ever be.
♪ We trace the roads ♪
Okay, got it.
♪ That never see an end ♪
So in your mind,
the probability of her being Spade Q is...
♪ We softly calm the hidden doubt ♪
Never mind, don't tell me.
I'll check for myself.
I'm still not used to you
talking so much all of a sudden.
♪ Seen in each other's eyes ♪
♪ Bring to life ♪
[The probability of Lin Wanxing
being Spade Q: 0%]
Okay.
Since she's been cleared of suspicion,
shouldn't you get going?
Where to?
Remember to check your phone later.
I'll send you information of
all the clubs that are interested in you,
especially Hengjiu.
I think I get what you mean
by that "especially."
Alright, I won't keep you in suspense.
I'm here
on a mission from my goddess.
She's offering a very high budget
and is determined to get you, Mr. Winfred,
to be the club coach.
I'm just here to lay the groundwork.
So, mission failed.
Seriously?
You're really going to be this ruthless
to your own buddy?
Give me my watch back.
I don't have it at the moment.
Besides,
you know perfectly well
what kind of person
your sister, my goddess, is.
Just you wait.
I...
You think I'm afraid of her?
But I am.
If she has something to say,
she can come and tell me herself.
Why send a minion over?
I'm just here to lay the groundwork.
I never intended to sway you or anything.
I wonder what that manager
wants with Winfred.
Maybe I should go and finalize
the coaching contract with him as well.
"The football team will train as usual.
But the indoor theory classes
need to be arranged
as soon as possible."
He still wants to have
indoor theory classes?
Doesn't sound like someone
who's planning to leave.
[Felix Yu, Manager of Yongchuan Hengjiu
Youth Football Club]
If he really leaves the football team,
what will happen?
Guess I'll cross that bridge
when I come to it.
I think
I'll give this to Lin Lu.
[Administrative Building]
Director Qian.
Director Qian?
Whenever I need him, he's never around.
Dear Director Qian,
with the exams approaching,
the team is in urgent need of...
Would that sound too formal?
[If I can save a heart
on the verge of breaking,]
[then I will not have lived this life
in vain.]
So Qian also reads poems?
Ms. Lin?
Director Qian.
Are you
looking for me?
Yes.
The football team needs an empty classroom
for tutoring sessions.
Have you tried
the Academic Affairs Office?
I have.
They said there are
no empty classrooms available.
So,
could you please step in
and help us out, Director Qian?
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do
about that.
You have to understand,
classrooms are reserved ahead of time,
and every room is already fully scheduled.
I can't just disrupt
other teachers' classes, right?
Try to figure something else out.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Good luck.
That was a really quick rejection.
"Handsome, kind-hearted,
gentle yet powerful,
the all-mighty Aladdin Qian Lamp:
Please grant us
a place for tutoring sessions.
Sincerely praying,
desperate Lin.
Come on, ladies first.
You go first.
Where did you go?
To buy drinks.
Continue.
What's this?
What is this thing?
Such ugly packaging.
Hold on.
Don't open it yet.
Could this be a bomb Wen Chengye planted
to get back at you?
-What are you talking about?
-What a waste.
It's not entirely impossible.
Have you ever received
anything weird like this before?
[100 free football equipment rentals]
A while ago, Qin Ao and the others
also received some weird stuff like this.
This...
Could this be another puzzle
from the mysterious person?
This is too much of a coincidence.
Open it and see.
[Destiny]
Why is there a question on this?
Destiny?
[Question 1] [Question 2]
Why are there questions in here?
[Chance]
Chance? These are also questions.
[Question 1] [Question 2] [Question 3]
[Map of Hongjing]
A map?
This string of numbers...
What does it mean?
Write it down first.
[Question 1] [Question 2] [Question 3]
I can't figure them out.
What do you have?
All questions we don't understand.
We don't know what they are either.
They're all math problems.
So the fun puzzles you were talking about
are just math problems?
Last time it was a word puzzle.
They were all four-character idioms.
At least I could understand them.
Among you,
whose math grades are better?
I think it's Yu Ming.
Yeah, he can score over 80.
Out of 100?
Out of 150.
I'll solve them then.
You should be the one doing it anyway.
After all, you're the genius
who can score 140 out of 150.
Show us what you've got, genius.
[Determinant of Matrix A]
[In the additive group of
residue classes modulo 4, Z4]
[What is the order of the element 2?]
The Destiny questions.
For Question 4, 5, and 6,
the answers I got
are 6, 6, and 1 respectively.
If we arrange the answers
for Chance and Fate questions
separately...
Look.
I get dizzy just looking at numbers now.
Then what's the connection
between these numbers?
The connection between the numbers
might not be important.
What's important
is their connection to the map.
[Xu] [Qing] [Wen] [Wang]
What's the connection?
Why are the questions divided into
2 parts, "Destiny" and "Chance"?
And why
[Xu] [Qing] [Wen] [Wang]
do both answers to Question 1
contain decimal points?
This is the map of Hongjing.
If there are numbers anywhere...
Exactly. They're coordinates—
latitude and longitude.
The patterns in these numbers
match the latitude and longitude
almost perfectly.
29.58? 106.53?
[Xu] [Qing] [Wen] [Wang]
So the intersection point is...
[Luoxin Photography Studio]
A photography studio?
Are we sure we're in the right place?
Don't worry.
Although math is my weak subject—
I only got 141 out of 150
on the college entrance exam—
I'm pretty sure I got it right.
We haven't used the code
on the back of this map yet.
Could it be related to this place?
Oh, right.
Now that you mention it,
I suddenly remember.
Photos from when we were kids
do usually have codes written on the back.
Fu, you're really smart.
Let's go in and ask.
-Come again.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Hi, excuse me.
Is this photo code from your shop?
In this day and age,
we don't register photos
with codes anymore.
Did you use them before?
I think our former boss
used them in the past.
Miss,
could you please check for us?
But I have urgent matters to handle
right now.
I'm sorry.
Maybe you could...
Thank you.
Let's step outside first.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
It's nothing.
Thank you, Miss.
Could it be that we got the answer
to the game wrong this time?
It can't be.
I think we just haven't found
the right answer yet.
[A Snapshot of Time]
A vintage photo-shoot event.
What if we go in for a photo-shoot?
Only couples and spouses can participate.
[Event Rules: Open only to
couples and spouses]
[Please make an appointment in advance.
Sessions will be arranged by appointment.]
Who's going?
Ms. Lin,
The only person we have here
who might be able to take couple photos
is you.
Ms. Lin, you're the only one
who can do it.
Ms. Lin, you're in your prime.
You might as well
take some photos as a keepsake.
It'll be a win-win.
Think about it, Ms. Lin.
[Little Savage Tribe]
It took us an hour
to solve the math problems,
but only 5 minutes to get kicked out.
So what do we do next?
Ms. Lin
needs to find someone
to take couple photos with
and sneak into the photo studio,
so as to continue finding clues.
How exciting!
What kind of spy movie plot is this?
Ms. Lin.
So have you found someone
to take couple photos with?
No.
I was wondering if it's really necessary
to go this far.
We don't even know
if the mysterious person
who sent the gift box
is just messing with us.
Don't you want to know the answer?
I do.
If it really comes down to it,
I might as well just hire someone.
It's only an act for the occasion anyway.
Anyone will do.
Ms. Lin.
My uncle is very easygoing,
and he has muscles.
He's very photogenic.
Ms. Lin.
My cousin's also about the right age.
How about I send you his pic?
Handsome, right?
My brother is also quite handsome.
The guy upstairs from me could do.
My cousin will definitely agree.
No need to ask.
Coach, what's wrong?
I saw the messages in the group chat.
If it's Saturday,
I have time.
Are you saying
you're willing to take couple photos
with me?
As for the specific fee,
let's settle it
based on the actual situation.
Words cannot express my gratitude.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
My grandpa's room.
Are we looking for something?
The clothes my grandpa and grandma
left behind.
That's a vintage photography studio,
you know.
I want to wear their clothes
to make it feel more ceremonial.
-Actually, I have...
-You look over there. I'll search this.
I haven't found anything yet.
What about you?
Here...
This amusement park
was the source of my childhood joy.
Grandpa used to take me there
all the time.
Grandpa and I even used to make bets
on who would get on the carousel first.
What's this?
Can you wiggle your ears?
Like this.
Impressive, right?
Impressive.
You try it.
Did they wiggle?
Formal name Lin Wanxing,
nickname Shining Star Genius...
Princess.
You're laughing at me.
I'm not laughing.
I could even see your teeth.
Still denying it.
You're still laughing.
I'm not laughing at you,
Shining Star Genius Princess.
Let's keep looking.
Found it.
Isn't this too small for me?
My grandfather was also very tall.
You can definitely fit into it.
Just make do with it.
Felix Yu,
[Felix Yu]
I have an honorable task for you:
go to my house and sneak out
a vintage suit for me.
Which house? In Hengjiu?
Yes.
What's going on? Cosplay?
I think I found my grandmother's too.
It should be this one.
They seem to be a set.
[Felix Yu]
❤️ උපසිරැසි ගැන්වුම Mflix විසින් ❤️
🔥 අලුත්ම Tv Series,Movies බලන්න Mflix එක්ක එකතු වෙන්න 🔥
Hello, hello, hello?
Where are you?
I don't need your help anymore.
You may leave.
Ms. Lin.
How do I look?
A bit less handsome than my grandpa.
Might as well commit to the act.
[A Snapshot of Time]
Hello, Boss.
We have a 1:30 appointment
for a couples' photo-shoot session.
Hello.
Okay.
Let me check.
Mr. Wang and Ms. Lin, right?
Yes.
Here are some styles for your reference.
You two can take a look first.
-Thank you.
-I'll go get ready.
No match.
Let's go check over there.
There are some more up here.
Boss, we'll wait for you upstairs.
Help yourselves.
[Golden Wedding Anniversary]
[August 23, 2021]
What's wrong?
Found it.
They're my grandparents.
Sorry
to keep you waiting.
We're all set for the photo-shoot.
Let me just adjust the lights.
Boss.
Excuse me, but
did you take this photo?
I didn't take this.
My dad took it.
This is his proudest work.
And he shot it with old-fashioned film.
See, he even numbered this photo.
Can you please sell it to me?
No can do. I'm sorry.
Please, Boss.
They were my closest family in this world.
And they are long gone.
I really want to buy it as a keepsake.
Please make an exception.
I'm sorry.
Let's just proceed with the photo-shoot.
[Golden Wedding Anniversary]
Are you guys Xunya and Yuanyuan?
You're here to pick up your photos, right?
Dad.
Why did you come downstairs?
This is my dad.
He's a bit...
He thinks it's still 30 years ago.
I've been waiting for you.
You're finally here.
I want to take another picture of you.
Get ready, you two.
Come on, get ready.
It seems this old gentleman
-is a friend of my grandparents.
-Do you mind letting my dad take the photos?
No problem.
T-Thank you.
I'll go get ready.
Could he be the one who led us here?
Are you alright?
I'll play along for now.
Oh no, it's blurry.
Let's try again.
Come on, get ready.
One, two...
What's going on?
It's still blurry.
I'm sorry, you two.
Sorry for wasting your time.
It's fine. We're not in a hurry.
Let's try again.
How about I do it, Dad?
Go away.
Use the tripod. Here.
Xunya.
Did you two have a fight?
-We didn't.
Then show me some chemistry.
Chemistry?
Chemistry.
He probably means
♪ I caught your eyes ♪
a little physical contact
♪ On the summer night ♪
and a brighter smile.
♪ A star that glows so bright ♪
This is good.
Come on.
Much better. Let's take another one.
♪ A spark in my heart ♪
Be closer.
♪ Disappear in my dream, secretly ♪
Ms. Lin, put your hand on my shoulder.
♪ With the evening breeze
whispering in my ear ♪
Look at me.
♪ Fireworks bloom across the sky ♪
♪ Shimmering in your eyes ♪
♪ And spreading into
a gentle sea of stars ♪
♪ Every night ♪
Good.
This one is good.
♪ I reach for starlight ♪
♪ Wandering through dreams with you ♪
♪ I follow the beat of my heart ♪
♪ Like dust floating in the air ♪
♪ Because of your love ♪
♪ I shine brilliantly ♪
Isn't the size a bit too big?
It's well taken.
We absolutely cannot let
those kids see this.
Are the photos ready?
This bracelet is...
You are...
Y-You're not Yuanyuan.
Who are you?
Yuanyuan was my grandmother.
My name is Lin Wanxing.
I'm the granddaughter of
Lin Xunya and Shen Shuyuan.
Right.
I just remembered
something very important.
[9 months ago]
Hello. Hello?
Excuse me,
are you the owner of this shop?
Are you here for a photo-shoot?
I'm here to collect a photo.
Come on in.
Lin Xunya.
Who are you?
Why didn't Xunya come
pick it up himself?
[Receipt]
Shortly after this photo was taken,
Mr. Lin was diagnosed with cancer.
He passed away not long ago.
What about his wife, Shen Shuyuan?
Mrs. Shen also passed away
not long after Mr. Lin did.
I see.
[Lin Xunya and Shen Shuyuan's
Golden Wedding Anniversary]
I really like this photo,
so I enlarged it
and kept it hanging upstairs.
I was planning
to take another photo for them
when they came to pick this one up.
Who would have thought...
At least
they're together again now.
Oh, by the way.
I have one more small request.
I hope you can do me this favor.
Since you know Xunya,
that makes you sort of a friend of mine.
Go ahead.
Open it and take a look.
I also have no idea
why he entrusted these things to me.
He said
that one day, Xunya's descendants
would come to collect them.
So I just accepted them in a daze.
Sir,
do you remember his name?
I don't think he left a name.
[No. 7, Wutong Road]
♪ Waiting for a dark cloud
to pass by you ♪
♪ Listen closely to its cries ♪
♪ The heavy rain will wash away
your reflection ♪
♪ And carry it toward distant scenery ♪
[No. 7, Wutong Road]
♪ Every experience has its meaning ♪
Give it to me.
♪ Scene by scene, they come together
to form who I am ♪
♪ Even the wounds
that leave behind their marks ♪
♪ Have taught me how to heal myself ♪
♪ The love I have given,
the love I have received ♪
Grandpa!
What brings you here, Wanxing?
I have something to tell you.
I saw a really big tadpole
♪ Every one of them gives me the strength
not to fear being hurt ♪
at school,
and I want to bring it home
and raise it into a frog.
Okay. Go find Grandma.
♪ Let my tears be carried away,
back into the ocean ♪
I'm in the middle of a class.
Be good.
Let's go to the yard.
Alright, where were we?
Here, "hold the line."
-And this.
-Don't make a sound.
♪ And blown toward flowers
blooming far away ♪
Let's go draw over there.
Come on.
Here, give me the bag.
♪ I fill the blank spaces of life
with colors ♪
Come on, sit here.
Okay, Grandma.
Grandma, time to draw.
What do you want to draw?
♪ My dreams are not afraid to awaken;
they continue to exist ♪
♪ I go beyond the dark clouds
and feel the haze disperse ♪
♪ Let me understand myself more clearly ♪
Bye.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Grandpa!
Look what I drew.
You drew so well.
What is it that you drew?
This is Grandpa,
this is me,
and this is Grandma.
You drew so well.
♪ Every experience has its meaning ♪
You won't be able to draw this
when you grow up.
Grandpa, your watch is so pretty.
♪ Scene by scene, they come together
to form who I am ♪
I want it too.
This was a gift
from Grandma.
♪ Even the wounds
that leave behind their marks ♪
This was given to me by your Grandma
on my first day as a teacher.
How can I just give it to you?
Grandma's being unfair.
♪ Have taught me how to heal myself ♪
You're still too young.
How about I buy you
a cartoon watch first, okay?
I want Grandpa's.
♪ I fill the blank spaces of life
with colors ♪
Alright, alright.
Once I retire from
Yuanyuan Tutoring Center,
I'll give you this watch.
Pinky swear.
♪ My dreams are not afraid to awaken;
they continue to exist ♪
Okay.
Pinky swear.
What does Yuanyuan mean?
[Yuanyuan Tutoring Center]
Yuanyuan.
Yuanyuan is Grandma's nickname.
♪ I go beyond the dark clouds
and feel the haze disperse ♪
Her parents gave her this nickname
with a special meaning.
"Yuanyuan" was meant to remind her
to study diligently.
♪ Let me understand myself more clearly ♪
“Yuanyuan" comes from
"the countless living beings."
[Yuanyuan Tutoring Center]
The purpose of studying is to care for
and serve all living beings.
♪ Take away my reflection ♪
Yuanyuan Tutoring Center?
Yuanyuan
♪ And go in search of distant scenery ♪
was my grandma's name.
My grandpa was a Chinese teacher,
and my grandma was an art teacher.
They taught for a lifetime,
and didn't stop after retiring.
This watch used to belong to my grandpa.
He promised
that once I grew up,
he'd give it to me.
Your grandpa took really good care of it.
It looks brand new.
Once I retire from
Yuanyuan Tutoring Center,
I'll give this watch to you.
Pinky swear.
Okay.
[Yuanyuan Tutoring Center]
“Yuanyuan" comes from
"the countless living beings."
The purpose of studying
is to care for and serve
all living beings.
I've made up my mind.
I will stay here
and tutor those kids.
For all living beings,
for the fruits of hard work—
what Grandpa and Grandma
devoted their lives to doing,
I'll carry it on for them.
Grandpa.
I think I finally understand
why you sent me to
Hongjing No. 8 High School.
Don't worry.
From now on,
I'll never give up on myself again
because of anyone.
Over this past month or so,
I've been really happy.
Thank you for your gift, Grandpa.
Grandpa,
Grandma,
I miss you so much.
Although I don't know
who the mysterious person is
or where he wants to lead us,
I can feel his kindness and help.
Maybe if we let nature take its course,
we'll eventually find out
who he really is someday.
Which number was it again?
-No. 7, I think.
-No. 7.
-Where is No. 7?
-This is No. 6.
-That one.
-This is No. 7.
-This is No. 5.
Here it is. Over here.
No. 7 is here.
It's so big.
-Do you think it's Ms. Lin's house?
-This is No. 7?
That's very likely.
Such a big house.
Why is it so run-down inside?
It's too heavy. Put it down for now.
-It's run-down.
-Hello? Anyone in there?
-There's no one.
-Anyone in there?
H-How could this be?
There are people here.
-Ms. Lin.
Coach.
It was Coach who asked us to come.
Ms. Lin, why are you here too?
Because this is the place where
you'll be having your tutoring sessions.
It's also our team's secret base.
Secret base?
This whole building?
We have such a big place to ourselves?
You see this?
This is pretty cool.
It's this clean?
This is the room.
It's a classroom.
Even the door's broken.
Yuanyuan Tutoring Center?
So
our secret base is called
Yuanyuan Tutoring Center.
How much longer do you think
it'll take us to finish cleaning today?
At least 3 or 4 hours.
Boss, are you wearing a watch?
Zheng is. What time is it?
Yeah, check what time it is.
Clean it properly.
Just do your own work.
You talk too much.
There are so many people here.
-Fu, you're here.
-Yes.
Come on, Fu.
Mop the outside first.
I'll help you first,
then you help me.
You guys be careful.
Ms. Lin.
If I'm not mistaken,
you've been wiping this marble counter
for 20 minutes.
I said we'd come clean this morning,
but I never meant this early.
I'm out of energy.
About to crash.
An hour in the morning
is worth two in the evening.
An hour in the morning is something
I simply can't afford.
You can still joke around.
It seems you're not really out of energy.
I've got a mission for you.
See that recliner over there?
I just cleaned it.
Go lie down there.
Whenever a mop comes by,
lift your legs up.
Think you can handle it?
Thank you.
-Mop.
-Where's the mop?
Right here.
Why is it so dirty?
Why is it so big?
It's too big, bro.
There's a balcony here.
How long will it take for us to clean?
Guys!
There's another huge balcony up here!
-Let's go take a look.
-Let's go.
The view is so nice.
We'll be having classes here from now on.
Yeah.
-This feels so great.
-We'll be having classes here.
Let's start sweeping from the bottom
and work our way up.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
♪ Night slips through my fingers ♪
♪ Embracing the coldness of wakefulness ♪
♪ Whispering my thoughts alone ♪
♪ Saying goodbye to the evening breeze
we met by chance ♪
♪ Staying with the jasmine blossoms
until late spring ♪
♪ Watching their elegance fade,
their fragrance disappear ♪
♪ I once dreamed of beauty ♪
♪ And I accept that
regrets may grow wild ♪
♪ Look, beneath the sunlight ♪
♪ In the dancing specks of dust ♪
♪ I'm grateful I never lost my sincerity ♪
♪ Or my gift for happiness ♪
♪ Sharing my warmth with a passing rain ♪
♪ Quietly feeling its journey ♪
♪ Like a firefly vanishing in an instant ♪
♪ Still beautiful in its entirety ♪
♪ There's no need to seek a final answer ♪
♪ Let the ending remain with
questions unanswered ♪
♪ No need to prove it with promises ♪
♪ The dusk when we once vowed
to stay together ♪
♪ No need to cling to forever ♪
♪ Allow separation to happen ♪
❤️ උපසිරැසි ගැන්වුම Mflix විසින් ❤️
🔥 අලුත්ම Tv Series,Movies බලන්න Mflix එක්ක එකතු වෙන්න 🔥